http://www.directed.com/legal/privacy

DIRECTED ELECTRONICS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT
Directed Electronics its subsidiaries and affiliate companies (“Directed”) understand that the protection and use of information provided by you to Directed is important to you. Directed is committed to maintaining your privacy. This Privacy Policy Statement sets out our information collection, use and dissemination practices for website (the “Website”). By visiting any of the Directed Website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement and hereby grant your consent to collect this information. Please read this Privacy Policy Statement to understand how Directed collects, uses and disseminates information through our Website.
What Personal Information About You Does Directed Collect?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on this Website or give us in any other way. This information includes demographic information and contact information such as names, addresses, phone numbers, fax numbers and email addresses. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features or conduct transactions.
Information Automatically Collected: Directed may also automatically collect non-personal information and data through the use of Cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to enhance your experience using our Website. Through cookies, a website can recognize repeat users, facilitate the user’s access to and use of the Website, and allow a site to track usage behavior. Examples of the information we may collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers.
The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of our Website’s features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. Directed uses one or more companies to place advertisements for our products and services and those of third parties on our Site and third-party sites.
Cookies and other technologies such as Web beacons or tags are used to measure the effectiveness of our ads and to determine the display of content and advertising to you based on your interests both on our site , as well as on third-party sites where you may visit.
To support this interest based advertising solution, we, and companies who we have contracted with, may use anonymous information about your visits to our and other Web sites. The information collected and used by this process is always anonymous, and does not enable any third-party to identify you individually.
How is Collected Information Used?
We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling your orders, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
Does Directed Share Information?
Directed is not in the business of selling your information to others. We share customer information only as described herein. We have controls that either are subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice.
Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: For certain transactions we work closely with our affiliated businesses to package, ship and fulfill your order. In other cases, we operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with these businesses. We may share customer information related to those transactions with third parties.
Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), measuring the effectiveness of our ads, determining the display of content, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes not described herein.
Promotional Offers: Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers you can let us know by sending an email to privacyofficer@directed.com.
Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy Statement (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Directed, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
Protection of Directed and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Directed, our shareholders, users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.
How Do I Grant Consent?
You hereby grant consent for Directed to collect the information as set out in this Privacy Policy Statement. Other than as set out above, you will not receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will not have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. You may withdraw or limit you consent by contacting Directed at privacyofficer@directed.com.
Although it is our hope that you find the display of advertising to you based on your anonymous interests valuable, if you would prefer not to participate in the services offered through these solutions, you can always opt-out of this activity by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website by clicking here.
What About Children?
It is Directed’s intention that our Website be use only by adults. Directed does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use the Website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. Directed does not knowingly send direct mailings to anyone under the age of 16.
What About Other Policies and Revisions?
If you choose to visit our Website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Use which are incorporated herein by reference, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of California. We encourage you to familiarize yourself.
Customize a security or remote start system that is perfect for your car.
Build Your System
Make the Right Choice!
Sign up to become an Authorized Directed Volume Dealer today
Sign Up Now!
Interested in contributing?
We appreciate your donation to help support Forte's misson
Donate Now!
